Can I put Andal in?
アンダル入れていい?
I want to play Andal.
アンダルしたい
Ah, that's amazing.
あーすごいよ
Does Andal feel good?
アンダル気持ちいいの?
It feels good.
気持ちいいよ
Andal feels really good.
アンダルめっちゃ気持ちいいよ
Andal is not gentle because it will break if you do it too hard.
アンダル激しくすると切れちゃうから優しくないんだ
Andal is seriously dangerous just by tapping it in the back.
アンダルって奥トントンするだけでマジでヤバい
Ah, it feels good.
あー気持ちいい
The kissing hole feels good.
キス穴気持ちいい
The previous Andal is completely gone.
前のアンダルすっかりだよ
It became sticky.
ベチャベチャになっちゃいました
Wait a minute, now.
ちょっと待ってね、今ね
I got a little wet there.
そこ濡れちゃったからね、ちょっとね
This will keep you hydrated.
こんな、水分補給する
I want to change my pet sheets right now.
ちょっと今、ペットシーツも変えたいな
Sorry.
ごめんね
Please wait a moment.
ちょっと待っててね
I'll come back with a ponytail.
ポニーテールにして戻ってくるから
Please wait a moment.
ちょっと待っててください
What do you feel the most about being the third one?
3個目だとどこが一番感じる?
Mmm, pussy.
う ーん、マンコ
Oisho.
おいしょ
terrible.
やばい
I dropped it.
落としちゃった
cool.
かっこいい
Warm pet sheets.
ペットシーツあったかい
Is it impossible to appear in Andal?
アンダルに出るのは無理?
It seems impossible.
無理そうだな
I've never done it before.
やったことないしな
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってね
I'll be back soon, so don't disappear.
すぐ戻ってくるから、いなくならないでね
Yes, sorry to have kept you waiting.
はい、お待たせしました
I'm home.
ただいまー
Would you like to have a cuppa time?
クパータイムしますか?
What do you think?
どうですか?
appear?
見える?
Hair tension.
お毛毛はりかけ
That's right.
そうなんだよね
Oh, open your fingers.
あ、手指開いて
That's no longer the case.
そうなくなった
I guess so.
そうかな
Blur your fingers.
手指をぼかして
More up-close.
もっとドアップで
More up?
もっとドアップ?
I'm a little nervous when I see them jumping around.
ぴょんぴょんを見て、ちょっとはりかけなの
It's disgusting.
気持ち悪いね
Did you include Chen Chen's Anhan?
チェンチェンのアンハン入れたの?
secret.
内緒
I'll leave it to your imagination.
想像にお任せします
Put in the red rubber.
赤ゴム入れて
appear?
見える?
Lift your butt up.
お尻を持ち上げてください
Andal is more open than there.
アンダルがそこよりも開いちゃってる
I want to include Chen Chen.
チェンチェン入れたいね
Even if you open it up to the point where it unfolds, it's impossible to do any more.
展開まで開いても、これ以上は無理
It's difficult, isn't it?
難しいんだよね
Yotsunbai.
よつんばい
Do you want to sleep?
よつんばいする?
Yotsunbai.
よつんばい
If it's only a little, I'll add a little.
少 しだったら、ちょっと入れちゃう
Spread it out.
広げて
My butt jiggles.
お尻プルプル
Yes, my butt is jiggling.
そう、お尻プルプルなのよ、私
Hey hey, let's masturbate again.
ねえねえ、またオナにしよう
Let's masturbate.
オナにしようよ
Let's do it.
しようしよう
I'm going to cry again.
泣いちゃうよ、また
I feel horny.
ムラムラする
It's been a tough week.
1週間大変だったわ
Were you all a trap?
みんな罠にしてましたか?
It got sticky again.
ベチャベチャにした、また
I'm so excited, it's amazing.
なんかピョンピョンしてる、すごい
What is this, a ninja?
何これ、忍者?
Awesome.
すげえ
If it's my finger, I can't do it.
指だと私、いけないから
I'll do this.
これでやる
I seriously can't go without a phone.
電話じゃないと私、マジでいけないんだよね
Let's jerk off, jerk off.
シコシコで、シコシコしよう
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I held back until I cried in the south.
南で泣くまで我慢した
TRUE?
本当?
Great.
えらい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
After all, this phone is the best.
や っぱ、この電話最強
It feels so good.
めっちゃ気持ちいい
I sprayed as much salt as I could.
思いっきり塩吹きまして
Because I blew a lot earlier.
さっきめっちゃ吹いちゃったからな
Just stop, stop breathing like a pussy.
ちょっとやめて、マンコの呼吸とかやめて
I laughed.
笑っちゃった
It's really interesting though.
めっちゃ面白いんだけど
It's really coming out now.
め っちゃめっちゃ出てたね、今
Did you see it?
見てた?
Properly.
ちゃんと
Messed up.
めちゃめちゃ
This way, this way.
こうしゅくしゅくして、こう
It's really bad, it's soaking wet.
マジでやばいよ、びしょびしょだよ
Things are getting serious.
大変なことになってきました
My computer is buzzing.
パソコンがぶしゅくしゅく
That's terrible.
やばいね
Bar time.
バータイム
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
My butt is already in trouble.
もうお尻が大変なことになっちゃった
Just change it once.
ちょっと一回交換ね
This is dangerous.
これがやばい
Sorry, I'm not gone.
ごめんね、いなくなってないよ
There is, though.
いるんだけどね
Will it come out again?
また出るかな?
I think it will go away if you drink tea.
お茶飲めば出ると思うよ
It's a little dark.
ちょっと暗い
More up?
もっとアップ?
Ah, it's already bad.
あー、もうやばいね
Covered in Cosecco.
コセッコまみれる
It's already hard.
もう大変だ
The construction has gotten really big.
作りがすごい大きくなっちゃった
No, that's amazing.
いや、すごいね
How many days has it been since?
何日ぶり?
It's on air pretty much every day.
割と毎日オンエアにしてるんだけどね
The only time I can blow it so hard is when I'm doing this stream.
こんなに思いっきり吹くのは、この配信やってる時だけだから
Let's do it.
やりしよう
No, I want to find it.
いや、見つけたいけどね
The camera is focused.
カメラが焦がれる
This one too.
これもこっち
If I can sleep, I might end up later than usual.
寝られるといつもより後半しちゃうかも
It's crazy, it's really perverted.
やばいよね、本当に変態だよね
Okay, I'll have some tea.
よし、ちょっとお茶飲むよ
I only have a little tea left.
もうお茶が少ししかない
Ah, tea is delicious.
あー、お茶うま
Are you back?
戻ってきた?
Yes, it's for replenishing drinks.
そう、飲み物補給だから
If you drink this tea normally, you will be able to blow.
普通にこのお茶飲むと吹ける
With tea.
お茶で
The tea makes me want to go to the bathroom.
お茶でトイレ行きたくなるから
I can only show you a little bit of my face.
顔はちょっとずつしか見せれないよ
No more.
もうダメ
Anyone who hasn't gone yet can go.
まだ行ってない人、みんな行けるよ
I think I'll try this.
これでやってみようかな
One more time.
もう一回
It's like the phone is flopping.
電話ドボドボみたい
do?
やる?
Oh, I'm going in, I'm going in.
あー、入っちゃう、入っちゃう
I'll be right in, already.
すぐ入っちゃうよ、もう
Look here.
ほら見て
Isn't it dangerous?
やばくね?
I'm already licked.
もうぺりぺりしちゃう
Oisho.
おいしょ
I have a very strong sexual desire, but I only have a strong sexual desire.
性欲強すぎなんですが、性欲ばかり強いよ
I wouldn't do something like this unless I was strong.
強くないとやらないよ、こんなこと
I really like being seen.
見 られるのめっちゃ好きだもん
Wait a moment.
ちょっと待ちます
ちょっと 待ちます
Add lotion.
ローション追加します
I'm getting really sluggish.
めっちゃズボってきた
Look.
ほら
Taran.
タラン
I'll pick up the phone again.
電話また入れちゃうよ
Like, put it in.
いいね、入れて
Feels good.
気持ちいい
this
この
Well, I want to go no-stop until 10 o'clock.
ま ま10時までノーストップで行きたいな
copper?
どう?
I was out of breath until 10 o'clock.
10時までずっと息もくる
I want to try it.
やってやりたいな
There's also anal.
アナルもいるよ
Like an endurance race
耐久レースみたいにな
That's it.
ってる
I'm going to put it in my anus.
ア ナル入れちゃうよ
I'm in.
入 っちゃったよ
It's so loud when you talk, so I'll show you my mouth.
口々ってうるさいから、しょうがないから口見せてあげるよ
Is it okay to do it like this?
こうやっていい?
I'm squirting so much my legs are cramping.
潮吹きすぎて足つる
I felt dehydrated and my legs felt stiff.
脱水みたいになって足つってきた
First of all, you're a demon, it's impossible.
まずして、鬼じゃん、無理
It gets in your eyes.
目につって入ったりする
I'll come in.
入るよ
Look.
ほら
Enter with plenty of time.
余裕で入る
I can't pee anymore.
もうおしっこ出ない
I'm seriously going to die.
マジで死ぬ
You know, my body right now.
分かるかな、私の体がさ、今
It's covered in pee.
めちゃめちゃおしっこまみれなの
appear?
見える?
Around here.
この辺とかは
Even my stomach was soaked.
お腹とかまでびっしょびしょなんだけど
No, it's harsh.
いやー、えぐい
I feel like I got really excited today.
今日めちゃめちゃカコイチ吹いた気がする
How was it?
どうでしたか?
It was amazing.
すごかったよね
It blew really hard today.
今日めっちゃ吹いたよね
Someone who has known Minami since the beginning.
みなみのこと最初の方から知ってる人
How many times today?
今日何回目の?
I forgot though.
忘れちゃったけど
Even people who have known you since the beginning.
最初の方から知ってる人でも
It was amazing, I guess.
すごかったよね、やっぱり
The bed.
ベ ッドが
This is terrible.
やばいよ、これは
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
My butt is all sticky.
お尻がべちゃべちゃ
It was amazing, seriously.
すごかったよね、マジで
Wait a minute, here's a comment.
ちょっと待って、コメントが
Very well done.
大変よくできました
thank you.
ありがとう
Today was amazing, wasn't it?
すごかったよね、今日
I want to clean it up at the end.
終わりに片付けてあげたい
It's actually a pee sheet.
ほ んとおしっこのシートがさ
I don't have a dog or anything.
犬とか飼ってないのにさ
Because this is what happens.
こんなことになるからさ
It was amazing, wasn't it?
すごかったでしょ、すごいでしょ
Really praise me.
ほんと褒めて
Canal was also amazing.
カナルもすごかった
thank you.
ありがとう
I'll come again, thank you.
また来ますね、ありがとう
I'm happy.
嬉しいよ
He will love the world.
世界を愛ってきてくれる
Maybe next week, maybe a weekday dog.
来週になるかな、平日のドッグかな
Stand up and show me your cracks.
立って割れ目見せて
crack.
割れ目
Butt tie.
お尻くっぱ
That's nice, Minami-chan.
さしいな、みなみちゃんは
real?
ほんと?
Who?
誰様?
Let the fluff grow out.
毛羽伸ばすの
What should I do?
どうしようかな
I'm lost.
迷ってる
Honesty.
正直
Especially because I'm not that picky.
別に私はこだわりそんなないから
Either one is fine, but anything other than Bo Bo would be fine.
ど っちでもいいんだけど、ボーボー以外だったら何でもいいかな
That's what it feels like.
って 感じ
Your ass was amazing today, really?
今日のお尻最高やった、ほんと?
thank you.
ありがとう
My legs are really cramping.
足がつる、ガチで
I can sleep well again today, that's true.
今日もねっくり寝れるね、ほんとだよ
It was a mess.
めちゃめちゃいったもん
Just be careful.
ちょっと気をつけして
Be careful.
気をつけ
When is the next time?
次回はいつ頃かな?
next week.
来週
It's seriously hydrating.
マジで水分とるね
I drank all the tea though.
お茶全部飲んじゃったんだけどさ
Can it be heart-shaped?
ハート型ってできんの?
I don't understand.
分 かんない
Butt tie.
お尻くっぱ
Impossible.
無理
I messed up a while ago.
さっきめっちゃしたもん
You've been showing your face for a while now.
さっきから顔めっちゃ見せてるもん
Should we all have saved up some salt?
み んな塩を溜めとけばよかったかな?
There's about 4 pet sheets worth of salt in there.
そこにペットシーツ4枚分ぐらいの私の塩があるよ
Anyone who wants it, please.
欲しい人どうぞ
Please come and get it.
取りに来てください
Show me your butt while sitting like a Yankee.
ヤンキー座りでお尻見せて
Is this okay?
これでいいのかね?
Let's drink tea.
お茶飲もう
I drank it all.
全部飲んじゃったぜ
I'm about to take a shower too.
そろそろ私もシャワー浴びてきます